Amirhossein SEFATI

Sasanipour Street, Tehran, Iran | +98 935 4237 134 ahsefati77@gmail.com | www.ahsefati.ir



Professional summary

Motivated "Computer Science" with 3 years of progressive experience in the Internet of Things (IoT) and protocols of networks layers. Offering expertise in programming with aptitude in learning new fields. Energetic self-starter and team builder able to navigate high-stress situations and achieve goals on time. Interested in field of Algorithms to improve Internet and Network design.

Work history

July 2019 - current

Industrial Server Designer for IoT devices

Tinaio co.

Tehran

- I design server and back-end programs. I want to know more about how to design algorithms for communications between devices to decrease costs and speedup responses.
- Simulating some parts of IoT devices for smart connecting with each other. I used to work
 with MQTT-SN protocol and it's algorithm to have smart devices connected to main server
 with lowest headers.
- · Familiar with "Wireshark" network analyzer.

October 2018 - current

Web Developer and Designer

Tipica co.

Tehran

- Designing, implementing and monitoring web pages and sites for continuous improvement in a fast-paced environment.
- Managing the team at meetings with executives, and discussing about project goals.
- Employing programming capabilities in PHP, MySQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Familiar with TCP/IP protocols and congestion control mechanisms.
- Familiar with Machine Learning concepts and basics with knowledge of python programming.

Skills

Electrical Skills:

- MATLAB programming
- Simulink simulations
- Proteus simulations
- Python programming
- Arduino programming (C++)
- ARM programming (C)
- Altium Designer

Computer Skills:

- Java programming
- JavaScript programming
- Php programming
- MySQL database
- HTML5 and CSS3
- Wireshark analyzer
- Data structure and Algorithm Design
- MQTT protocol

Education

2016-current

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Having an "A" GPA
- Working in Innovation and Technology Center (ITC) in Electrical engineering department
- Holding and teaching "IoT platform design" course in ITC
- Participating in several conferences about Industrial problems and how to solve them with low-budget

2018-current

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Field of "Software engineering"
- Having an "A" GPA
- Participating in several labs about Software design, Operating systems,
 Computer network, Multi-Thread programming and etc
- Creating a web-app site for projects about developing online services in some courses
- Interested in creating simulator and plotter apps like MATLAB-Simulink

2020 - current

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Field of "Artificial Intelligence"
- Having an "A" GPA
- Interested to create simulations of human and behavior of him/her.

Tips:

- I study Electrical and Computer engineering in Amirkabir university simultaneously having two separate student IDs for each of them. In our education system, students of "Computer Engineering" must study in two fields! So I study "Software Engineer" and "Artificial Intelligence".
- I am so interested in learning new things and in my opinion, I always learn fast!
- I have this ability to work and study all day long.



Amirkabir University of Technology **B.Sc.** Transcript

First name: AMIRHOSSEIN Student No.: 9523076

SEFATI Last name: Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Semester Status: Normal

Electrical Engineering-Electrical Engineering Department:

First Semester 2016 - 2017 (1395 - 1396)

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Math. (I)				1011053	3	15.25	
General Physics (I)				1021303	3	15.75	
General Physics (II)				1021353	3	14.5	
Islamic Thought (I)				1051122	2	19.5	
English for the Student	ts of Engineering			1061103	3	17.03	
Computer Programmin	ıg			2302023	3	18.5	
Electricity Lab.				2302511	1	19	
Taken Units: 18	Passed Units: 18	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	W	thdrawn Un	hits: 0 Average: 16.73
Total Taken Units: 18	Total Passed Units: 18	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	wn Units: 0 Total Average: 16.73

Second Semester 2016 - 2017 (1395 - 1396)

Second Semester 2016 -	2017 (1395 - 1396)						Semester Status: Normal
Course Title					Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Math. (II)				1011103	3	17.43	
Differential Equations				1011253	3	16.5	
Numerical Analysis				1011402	2	17.75	
General Physics Lab (I)				1022371	1	20	
Farsi				1051203	3	19	
Islamic Rev. of Iran				1051412	2	19.75	
Probability & Statistics				2302013	3	17.2	
Electric Circuits (I)				2305033	3	19	
Taken Units: 20	Passed Units: 20	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0	W	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 18.12
Total Taken Units: 38 Total Passed Units: 38 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Inef			fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 0 Total Average: 17.46	

First Semester 2017 - 2018 (1396 - 1397)

First Semester 2017 - 2	018 (1396 - 1397)						Semester Status: Norma
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Modern Physics				1021253	3	17.5	
Islamic Thought (II)				1051132	2	19	
Electric Circuits Lab				2302061	1	19.5	
Engineering Mathematic	s			2303043	3	16.75	
Electric Circuits (II)				2305063	3	17.8	
Electromagnetics				2305073	3	14.25	
Eletronics (I)				2305093	3	17	
Taken Units: 18	Passed Units: 18	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 17.08
Total Taken Units: 56	Total Passed Units: 56	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	То	tal Withdrav	wn Units: 0 Total Average: 17.34

Second Semester 2017	- 2018 (1396 - 1397)						Semester Status: Normal
Course Title					Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Physical Education (I) *	Physical Fitness			1040211	1	18.5	
the History of Islamic C	Culture & Civilization			1051032	2	19.5	
Eletronics Lab. (I)				2302091	1	19	
Electronics (II)				2305113	3		WITHDRAWN
Electrical Machines (I)				2305153	3	17.2	
Logic Circuits				2305183	3	13.5	
Signals & Systems				2305213	3	14.6	
Technical English				2307002	2	18.5	
Research Methods & Ro	eport Writing			2384132	2	19	
Taken Units: 20	aken Units: 20 Passed Units: 17 Failed Units: 0 Ineffecti		Ineffective	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 3 Average: 16.91
otal Taken Units: 76 Total Passed Units: 73 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Inet			fective Units: 0	То	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 3 Total Average: 17.24	

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title	Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Physical Education (II) * Hockey	1040161	1	18.5	



Amirkabir University of Technology B.Sc. Transcript

First name: **AMIRHOSSEIN** Student No.: 9523076

Last name: **SEFATI** Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Electrical Engineering-Electrical Engineering Department:

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Practical Mysticism in	Islam			1051322	2	19.5		
Electronics (II)				2305113	3	12		
Linear Control Systems			2305243	3	10.1			
Communication Systems (I)		2305273	3	17.6				
Taken Units: 12	Passed Units: 12	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 14.72
Total Taken Units: 88 Total Passed Units: 85 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Ineffe		fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	wn Units: 3	Total Average: 16.88		

Second Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Second Semester 2018	8 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)							Semester Status: Normal
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Quran Interpretation				1051532	2	18.5		
Logic Circuits Lab				2302181	1	20		
Linear Control Systems	s Lab.			2302241	1	19.25		
Digital Control System	ıs			2304003	3	13.75		
Digital Control System	s Lab.			2305241	1	19.12		
Instrumentation		2356123	3	16.64				
Taken Units: 11	Γaken Units: 11 Passed Units: 11 Failed Units: 0 Ineffecti		Ineffective	e Units: 0	W	ithdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 16.96
Total Taken Units: 99	tal Taken Units: 99 Total Passed Units: 96 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Ine			fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 3	Total Average: 16.89

Summer 2019 (1398) Semester Status: Normal

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Training				2347562	2	19.25	
Taken Units: 2	Passed Units: 2	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 19.25
Total Taken Units: 101 Total Passed Units: 98 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Inefi		fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	wn Units: 3 Total Average: 16.94		

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

First Semester 2019 - 2	020 (1398 - 1399)							Semester Status: Normal
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Instrumentation Lab				2305251	1	20		
Industrial Control				2309173	3	17.3		
Modern Control				2356113	3	14.6		
Taken Units: 7	Passed Units: 7	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 16.53
Total Taken Units: 108	Total Passed Units: 105	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	vn Units: 3	Total Average: 16.91

Second Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

Second Semester 2019 -	2020 (1398 - 1399)							Semester Status: Norm	ıal
Course Title	Course Title					Sc./Deg.		Comments	
Electrical Machines (I) Lab.				2302151	1			UNRECEIVED	
Indust. Control Lab				2302171	1			UNRECEIVED	İ
Special Topics (Electrical and Electronic Measurement Systems)				2311072	2			UNRECEIVED	İ
Project	Project				0			IN PROGRESS	
Taken Units: 4	Passed Units: 0	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Uni	ts: 0	Average: 0	
Total Taken Units: 112	otal Taken Units: 112 Total Passed Units: 105 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Ir			fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdraw	n Units: 3	Total Average: 16.91	

This is an unofficial transcript issued solely for the student information and possible use for provisional admission to the graduate school. The official transcript will be provided upon formal request to: Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Amirkabir University of Technology, P.O.Box 15875-4413 Tehran, Iran, registraroffice@aut.ac.ir

Not valid without signature and authorized seal of the registrar, both on the transcript and the envelope.



Amirkabir University of Technology B.Sc. Transcript

First name: **AMIRHOSSEIN** Student No.: 9531702

Last name: **SEFATI** Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Computer Engineering-Computer Engineering Department:

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

First Semester 2018 -	2019 (1397 - 1398)							Semester Status: Normal
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Discrete Mathematics				3101033	3	17.75		
Advanced Programmir	ng			3101043	3	19.25		
Advanced Programmir	ng Lab.			3101051	1	19.25		
Special Topics (Applie	ed Linear Algebra)			3102103	3	14.1		
Taken Units: 10	Passed Units: 10	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	W	ithdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 17.26
Total Taken Units: 10	tal Taken Units: 10 Total Passed Units: 10 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Inc			fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	vn Units: 0	Total Average: 17.26

Second Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Data Structures and Algo	orithms			3102033	3	15.5		
Computer Architecture				3102073	3	17.95		
Computer Architecture I	Lab.			3102081	1	17.95		
Taken Units: 7	Passed Units: 7	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 16.9
Total Taken Units: 17 Total Passed Units: 17 Total Failed Units: 0 Total Ine			fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 0	Total Average: 17.11	

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399) Semester Status: Norma										
Course Title	Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments					
Principles of Database	3102313	3	16.12							
Microprocessor and Assembly Language				3103013	3	19.6				
Microprocessor and Assembly Language Lab.				3103021	1	19.6				
Operating Systems				3103033	3	16.4				
Operating Systems Lab	3103041	1	20							
Computer Networks	3103053	3	16.1							
Computer Networks La	3103061	1	16.1							
Taken Units: 15	Passed Units: 15	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Withdrawn Units: 0 Ave		Average: 17.36			
Total Taken Units: 32	Total Passed Units: 32	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	ffective Units: 0 Total Withdrawn Units: 0 Total Ave		Total Average: 17.23				

Second Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

Second Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399) Semester Status: Normal										
Course Title					Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments			
Theory of Machines and I	Languages			3102093	3		UNRECEIVED			
Algorithm Design				3102213	3		UNRECEIVED			
Principles of Compiler Design					3		UNRECEIVED			
Software Engineering I				3103073	3		UNRECEIVED			
Taken Units: 12	Passed Units: 0	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0 Withdrawn Units: 0		ithdrawn Units	s: 0 Average: 0			
Total Taken Units: 44	Total Passed Units: 32	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	ffective Units: 0 Total Withdrawn Units: 0		tal Withdrawr	1 Units: 0 Total Average: 17.23			

This is an unofficial transcript issued solely for the student information and possible use for provisional admission to the graduate school. The official transcript will be provided upon formal request to: Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Amirkabir University of Technology, P.O.Box 15875-4413 Tehran, Iran, registraroffice@aut.ac.ir

Not valid without signature and authorized seal of the registrar, both on the transcript and the envelope.